

## **Htet Htet Win(Monica)**

## Quality Assurance Engineer / Software Tester/Test Analyst

- htethtetwinn.qa@gmail.com
- monicaminzy.github.io

- +65 88259053 (WhatsApp,Viber,Call)
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/htethtetwinn-monica-8396191a3/

Resourceful Software Quality Assurance Tester with nearly 3 years of solid experience in the banking and mobile wallet sectors. Proficient in Functionality Testing, Integration Testing, System Testing, and Regression Testing of Client/Server, Web-based, and mobile applications.

Demonstrate excellent abilities in analyzing requirements, creating test plans, designing and developing test cases based on business requirements. Possesses extensive knowledge and experience across all stages of the Software Development Life Cycle (SDLC), from initiation and definition to deployment and support.

### **Experience**

# Platform Quality Assurance Engineer WavePay (Digital Mobile Wallet) | Yoma Bank

May 2023 - February 2024

Wave Money is a mobile financial services provider in Myanmar.

#### Responsibilities

- Primarily focused on manual test activities, dedicating 75% to tasks involving customer, channel, and merchant applications of WavePay, while allocating the remaining 25% to automation test activities.
- Responsible to create and maintain test case documentation based on product and technology requirements and design documents.
- Perform manual and some automated UI automation testing by utilizing Appium server & API testing (Cypress) in offline biller Project of customer WavePay application.
- Conducting real-time online testing of the WavePay app and browser compatibility by utilizing LambdaTest software on cloud-based real device farm.
- Analyzing UAT test results to identify and effectively document bugs, collaborating closely with development teams to ensure timely resolution.
- Work with the SCRUM MASTER to ensure that all user stories have well-defined acceptance criteria, test plans, and any hooks needed to enable testability .
- Leading platform changes related to push notifications within the WavePay customer app, focusing on cost reduction and the implementation of the Etrade SMS project.

# Senior User Acceptance Test Analyst KBZPay(Digital Mobile Wallet) | KBZ Bank

June 2022 - May 2023

KBZPay is a mobile wallet powered by KBZ Bankin Myanmar.

#### Responsibilities

 Testing and analyst on released version and off released version of customer and partner application of KBZPay.

- Responsible for managing the user acceptance testing process to ensure the delivery of working software that aligns with business requirements.
- Collaborating closely with Product Owners and the technology team for issue tracking, reporting, and resolution.
- Preparing and collecting Test Results, Accounting Entries and Customer Journey.
- Translating business requirements/functional specifications into effective test cases.
- Executing test scripts, documenting defects in the tracking system (Jira), performing API Testing utilizing Postman and overseeing defect resolution processes.
- Testing seasonal festival and promotional campaigns in KBZPay customer app.

### Junior Dev Support & QA Engineer

January to April 2022

#### Myanmar Digital Solutions (MMDS) Pte Ltd

MMDS is consulting company that provides digital solutions .

#### Responsibilities

- Responsible for a range of web and mobile software applications developed by the company to serve both domestic and international clients.
- Developing test cases and scenarios for new product releases, and conducting System Integration Testing (SIT) and User Acceptance Testing (UAT) to identify and address potential product issues.
- Performed functional testing, exploratory testing, end-to-end testing, cross-browser testing, and usability testing for websites, apps, web apps, and desktop applications(Sectors: Medical, B2B, E-commerce service, Video, own E-learning portal service).

#### **Junior Software Engineer**

**July 2020 to January 2021** 

#### Myanmar Information Technology (MIT)Co., Ltd

MIT is tech company focusing on Enterprise Solution development and delivery to customers.

#### Responsibilities

- · Generate Crypto material for new peer.
- Editing chain code in test-network, editing API in test-network in blockchain & generate crypto material for new peer.
- Create configuration for the new peer and bring up the container Observing new channel and chaincode in Hyperledger fabric 2.0.

#### Education

#### **Yatanarpon Cyber City University**

Dec 2012 - October 2019

• Bachelor of Information Science & Technology B.E (IST) (2020 graduated)

#### Skills

- Manual Testing & Coding Skills
- API Testing (Postman)
- JIRA( issue tracking software)
- Execution of test cases and test scripts using Microsoft Excel
- PHP,JavaScript,Python,MySQL Database

- Automated testing experience of Appium & Selenium
- API testing using Cypress
- Version Control: Git
- lambdatest(online-device-farm)l
- · Excellent Attention to detail